Tiffany Wu

Phone: (408) 430-3731 | Email: tiffanywu404@gmail.com | Sunnyvale, CA |

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/tiffany-wu-5683812b6

Portfolio: https://tiffanywu.work/

Junior user interface and user experience designer passionate about developing cutting-edge digital products. Certificate in UX/UI Design from University of Berkeley, California. Fine arts and sociology background that translate to strengths in aesthetics and research skills, making a valuable addition to any team.

Technical Skills

Technical: Figma, Google Suite, Adobe Creative Suite, HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap **UX/UI Design Tools:** Atomic Design, UI Grids and Composition, Heuristic Evaluation, Typography, Imagery, Color Theory, Interaction Design and Iconography, Storyboarding, Decision Flow Diagrams, User Need Identification, User Experience Interviewing, Persona Creation, Insight Synthesis

Additional: Copy Writing, Project Management, Presenting

Selected Projects

Cuesine App | https://motiff.github.io/CaseStudy2/

The aim of this project was to empower busy individuals to cook more by offering an app that simplifies the process of finding and planning meals.

- Skills Used: Stakeholder Interviews, User Research (Interviews + Surveys) & Analysis, Persona Creation, User Experience Design (UI/UX), Interaction Design, Prototyping, In-Person and Remote User Testing
- Technologies Used: Figma, Miro, Trello, Google Suite, Slack, Zoom
- Team of three other UI/UX design students

Dream Center Website Redesign | https://motiff.github.io/Module-20/

Dream Center is a Los Angeles-based non-profit organization that provides support to those affected by homelessness, hunger, and the lack of education. The goal of this project was to redesign the Dream Center website with a focus on addressing the pain points of potential nonprofit organization volunteers and donors, namely the need for transparency, easier viewing of and sign up for events, and a personalized user experience that motivates them to contribute more. The redesign involves improvements to readability and new designs for systems such as an interactive impact report and donation tracker, event calendar, and user dashboard.

- Skills Used: Stakeholder Interviews, User Research (Interviews + Surveys) & Analysis, Persona Creation, User Experience Design (UI/UX), Interaction Design, Prototyping, In-Person and Remote User Testing
- Technologies Used: Figma, Miro, Trello, Google Suite, Slack, Zoom
- Team of four other UI/UX design students

Work Experience

Amazon Lab 126 06/2022 - 11/2022

Business Service Center Associate

Sunnyvale, CA

 Provided customer service at a front desk and managed shipments in a corporate environment.

Superior Court of California

12/2022 - 5/2023

Legal Process Clerk

Palo Alto, CA

• Provided customer service at a front desk, performed data entry, and other duties in a government environment.

Volunteer Experience

Aid Coordinator, South Bay Mutual Aid

09/2020 - 12/2020

 Matched aid requests to volunteers through use of Airtable and contact through phone, text, and email.

Propaganda Committee Member, Anakbayan San Jose

02/2019 - 09/2019

- Designed and created flyers and images using Canva.
- Wrote, prepared, and presented information at meetings.
- Managed and wrote social media posts.
- Offered and implemented feedback on the organization's events.

Education

Certificate in UX/UI Design University of California, Berkeley April 2024

Website Design Class taken at Foothill College August 2023

User Experience (UI/UX) Design Class taken at Foothill College August 2023

Bachelor of Arts in Sociology University of California, Irvine March 2022 Associate of Arts in Sociology for Transfer (AA-T), Cum Laude De Anza College September 2019